RAEVEN GONÇALVES



- Mirandela, Bragança
- 960214943
- raevengoncalves@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Committed professional offering more than 15 years of experience in a variety of fields. Excellent communication skills and a consistent team player in all sorts of environments. Seeking to expand talents, learn and grow in a well-established company.

EXPERIENCE

Independent Contractor, 06/2018 - Current Self Employed, Mirandela, Portugal Handyman and general construction and installation

New Business Development Manager, 07/2010 - 01/2017

ZD Marketing, Johannesburg, South Africa

• Obtained, managed, grew and maintained new and existing corporate clientele.

Warehouse and Stores Manager, 06/2009 - 06/2010

Powermac, Johannesburg, South Africa

• Ran, managed and maintained the productivity and smooth running of the warehouse and stores, the staff and the stock.

Motor Technician, 08/2008 - 03/2009

Toyota, Johannesburg, South Africa

Repaired and inspected motor vehicles for services and/or with damage.

Inventory Manager, 01/2002 - 07/2008

Matters Marketing, Johannesburg, South Africa

 Responsible for all logistics, receiving of stock and the dispatching of orders for timeous delivery to customers

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Front-end development
- Web-based software engineering
- Testing and maintenance
- HTML and XML
- JavaScript

- Website design
- Git
- React
- Shopify

EDUCATION

EPICODE, July 2022

Front End Web Developer

• Coursework in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Typescript, Agile methodologies, Heroku, Visioning (Git/GitHub), data structure and algorithms.

FreeCodeCamp, February 2022

• Responsive Web Design

Codecademy, 2022

- React
- JavaScript

DataCamp, 2022

• Python Basic Fundamentals

SOFT SKILLS

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Negotiation
- Creativity
- Problem Solving
- Interest in lifelong learning